Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- P, Series XVI
  - Plans and Budgets / Reports and Statements
    - Non-Formal Education: P-09.14.01/1982 - P-09.14.01/2002, 1982-2002 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Health Services Office and Smaller Projects: P-09.21.01/1969 - P-09.21.01/2002, 1969-2002 (Box 133, Folder 1-4)
    - Okhaldhung Project: P-09.22.01/1961 - P-09.22.01/2002, 1961-2002 (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
    - Shanta Bhawan Project (Hospital, CHP, N. Campus): P-09.23.01/1954 - P-09.23.01/1982, 1954-1982 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - CPHCP / CDAP/ CDHP, Lalitpur / YALA: P-09.24.01/1982 - P-09.24.01/1993, 1982-1993 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Lalitpur Nursing Campus: P-09.25.01/1982 - P-09.25.01/2002, 1982-2002 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Patan Hospital: P-09.26.01/1976 - P-09.26.01/2002, 1976-2002 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Palpa Project: P-09.27.01/1954 - P-09.27.01/2002, 1954-2002 (Box 136, Folder 1-4)
    - Gorkha Project: P-09.28.01/1958 - P-09.28.01/2002, 1958-2002 (Box 135, Folder 7-9)
    - Bhaktapur (Bhatagaon) Project: P-09.29.01/1958 - P-09.29.01/1974, 1958-1974 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Rural Development Office and Smaller Programs: P-09.41.01/1990 - P-09.41.01/2002, 1990-2002 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Rural Development Centre: P-09.42.01/1979 - P-09.42.01/2002, 1979-2002 (Box 134, Folder 7-8)
    - Surkhet Project: P-09.43.01/1980 - P-09.43.01/1999, 1980-1999 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Buling / Arakhala (Nawal Parasi Hills Dev. Project): P-09.44.01/1979 - P-09.44.01/1985, 1979-1985 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Okhaldhunga Rural Development Project: P-09.45.01/1990 - P-09.45.01/2002, 1990-2002 (Box 136, Folder 6-7)
    - Butwal Projects: P-09.56.01/1964 - P-09.56.01/1982, 1964-1982 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Butwal Projects: P-09.56.01/1983 - P-09.56.01/1993, 1983-1993 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - Andhikhola Project: P-09.57.01/1979 - P-09.57.01/1998, 1979-1998 (Box 135, Folder 4-5)
    - Jhimruk Project: P-09.58.01/1989 - P-09.58.01/2000, 1989-2000 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Khimti Project: P-09.59.01/1994 - P-09.59.01/1999, 1994-1999 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Melamchi Project: P-09.60.01/1993 - P-09.60.01/1998, 1993-1998 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Publicity:
    - Films: P-10.02.01/0001 - P-10.02.01/0004 - RESTRICTED, 1963-1983 (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
      Correspondence re. Caravs (1963-1966), Nepal on the Potter's Wheel (1968), Living Water (1976), The Pipel Tree (1983)
    - Miscellaneous: P-10.02.01/0005 - RESTRICTED, 1963-1994 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      Includes some scripts for old slide sets; others with AV material
    - Books and Booklets: P-10.01.01/0001 - P-10.01.01/0003 - RESTRICTED, 1978, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 8-9)
      Correspondence about Use It In Service, Greetings From Nepal, Nepal on the Potter's Wheel, Nepal and the Gospel of God
  - Other P
    - Presbyterian Church, USA: P-11.00.01-P-11.00.02: - RESTRICTED, 1954-1972 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
      Correspondence, annual statistics, Fifty Million Fund
    - Presbyterian Church in Canada: P-12.00.01 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Presbyterian Church Synod, Mizoram: P-13.00.01 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Presbyterian Church in Ireland: P-14.00.01 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Personal Counsellor: P-15.00.01 - RESTRICTED (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Pyersingh / Paimey: P-16.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1963, 1983-1984 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Padma Sadan: P-17.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1972, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Protestant Congregation (KICC): P-18.00.01 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Property (Land and Buildings): P-19.00.01, 1963, 1966 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Prayer Calendar / Personnel Directory: Combined Prayer Calendar and Personnel Listing: P-20.01.01, 1972-1993 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Prayer Calendar (Separate): P-20.02.01/0001 - P-20.02.01/0018, 1994-2006 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Directory: P-20.03.01, 1989-2006 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Directories, various: (P-20.03) (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Prayer Calendar Committee minutes and correspondence: P-20.04.01 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Prayer Calendars and prayer bulletins: (P-20) (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Pre-1954: P-21.00.01
      Material has been handed over to the Nepal Church History Project so that the whole Mission / church story prior to 1954 may be kept together. Particular files include: Nepal Border Fellowship, Duncan Hospital Bihar, RBMU Bihar, WMPL Darjeeling, C of S Darjeeling, ZBMN Nantanwa, FCF (EFCF) Darjeeling
    - The Poor: P-22.00.01/0001 - P-22.00.01/0016, 1991-1994 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      Includes Task Force records, questionnaire on identifying the poor.
    - Program Unit Directors' Meetings: P-23.00.01/0001 - P-23.00.01/0004, 1997-1999 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Program Unit Directors' Meetings: minutes: (P-23.01), 2000-2001 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - People Energy & Environment Development Association (PEEDA): reports: (P-026.01), 1998-2006 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - People Energy & Environment Development Association (PEEDA): correspondence: (P-026.02) - RESTRICTED, 2004-2006 (Box 220, Folder 7)
- Q, Series XVII
  - Q-10.07.24 (Box 173, Folder 3)
- R, Series XVIII
  - Various R
    - Resignations: R-01-00-01 - RESTRICTED, 1984-19986 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      Study of reasons for resignations made in 1984-1986 on people who had left in previous 12 years or so.
    - Regions Beyond Missionary Union: R-02.00.01 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      General correspondence; includes J. Lindell letter on the purpose of the UMN, July 1963
    - Royal Family: R-03.00.01/0001 - R-03.00.01/0038 - RESTRICTED, 1970-2001 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence, reports
    - River Rover: R-04.00.01/0001 - R-04.00.01/0002 - RESTRICTED, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Rural Youth Training Program: R-05.00.01/0001 - R-05.00.01/0026, 1977-1991 (Box 139A, Folder 1-2)
    - Roman Catholics: R-06.00.01 (Box 139A, Folder 3)
  - Reference Files / Manuals
    - Business and Policy Manual, Ready Reference, Orientation Manual, etc.: R-07.00.01/0002 - R-07.00.01/0005, 1972-1991 (Box 139A, Folder 4-7)
    - Re. Constitution, Board, Executive Committee, Finance, Appointments, Personnel - RESTRICTED (Box 139A, Folder 8-9)
  - Rural Development General
    - Reports, etc.: R-09.01.01/0001 - R-09.01.02/0046, 1976-2000 (Box 139B, Folder 1-9)
    - Reports, etc.: R-09.01.01/0057, R-09.01.01/0066, R-09.01.01/0078 (Box 166, Folder 2, 3)
    - Reports, etc. - Report of RD Seminar, "Rapid Rural Appraisal Process": R-09.01.01/0084, R-09.01.01/0116, 1988,1992 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Reports, etc. - "RDD Program Review": R-09.01.02/0042, 1999 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Energy Seminars: R-09.02.01/0010 - R-09.02.01/0015, 1976, 1978, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      SATA Seminary, Kathmandu; UMN Seminary, Tansen; DCS Seminar, Butwal
    - Community motivation / people's participation: R-09.03.01/0001-R-09.03.01/0020, 1976-1991 (Box 140, Folder 7-8)
    - Drinking Water Program: R-09.04.01/0001 - R-09.04.01/0027 -R-09.04.01/0047, 1977-1998 (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
    - Forestry: R-09.05.01/0001 - R-09.05.02/0034, 1974-1999 (Box 141, Folder 1-7)
    - Forestry - "Introduction to Policy ...of CFD": R-09.05.01/0013, 1982 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Forestry: R-09.05.01/0056, R-09.05.01/0082 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Forestry: Re. Bamboo: R-09.05.01/0102, 1991 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Forestry Re. Bamboo:: R-09.05.01/0103, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Forestry: Report of Forestry meeting: R-09.05.01/0123, 1993 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Forestry: - Proceedings and papers of Forestry meetings: R-09.05.02/0008/001, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - IDC Minutes in bound book: R-09.06.01 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: R-09.07.01/0001 - R-09.07.01/0018 - RESTRICTED, 1979-1987 (Box 131, Folder 4-5)
  - Rural Development Department
    - Reports, etc. - see also Rural Development General: R-10.01.01/0001- R-10.01.01/0005, 1988-1993 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Reports, plans, etc.: R-10.01), 1997-2000 (Box 220, Folder 8-9)
    - Reports, plans, etc.: R-10.01), 2001-2003 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Performing Arts Troupe: R-10.02.01/0001-R-10.02.01/0006, 1988-1990 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project: R-10.03.01/0001 - R-10.03.01/0006, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project: R-10.03.01/0007 -R-10.03.01/0046, 1990-1996 (Box 142A, Folder 1-4)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project:R-10.03.01/0011 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - NCRP Final Summary Report: R-10.03.01/0024/006, 1993 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - "A process approach as the means and end of rural community development": R-10.03.01/0026, 1993 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - Participatory evaluation: R-10.03.01/0044/001, 1995 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project: R-10.03.02/0000 - R-10.03.02/0038, 1996-1998 (Box 142B, Folder 1-2)
      Continued in R-10.09.01 Dhaking Resource Management Project and R-10.10.01 - Ramechhap Com. Dev. Project
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - Participatory evaluations: R-10.03.02/0003/003, R-10.03.02/0002/001, 1996 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - Thekre Participatory evaluation: R-10.03.02/0019/001 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - Annual report: R-10.03.02/0031, 1998 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project - "Participatory Evaluations in Practice...": R-10.03.02/0035, 1998 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project: R-10.03.02/0036, R-10.03.02/0037, R-10.03.02/0039, R-10.03.02/0042 (Box 171, Folder 2,3)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit: R-10.04.01/0000 - R-10.04.01/0040, 1991-1997 (Box 142B, Folder 5-7)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit - "Supporting National NGOs....": R-10.04.01/0006, 1992 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit: - "Review of RDD approaches...": R-10.04.01/0030, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit: - "LDG Organizational Assessment training manual": R-10.04.01/0052, 1998 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit: R-10.04.01/0040 - R-10.04.01/0062, 1997-1999 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Program and Nepali Organizations Unit: R-10.04.02/0001 - R-10.04.02/0009 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Unit: reports: R-10.04), 1995-2001 (Box 221, Folder 2-5)
    - (Nepali) NGO Support Unit: reports: R-10.04), 2002-2003 (Box 222, Folder 1-2)
    - Village Leathercraft Training: R-10.05.01/0001 - R-10.05.01/0021, 1990-1999 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Village Leathercraft Training - "Village Leathergoods": R-10.05.01/0004, R-10.05.01/0005, R-10.05.01/0008, R-10.05.01/0009, 1991-1995 (Box 171, Folder 3, 4)
    - Village Leathergoods Training Assoc.: General, reports, etc.: R-10.05), 1991-2005 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Nepal Resource Management Project: R-10.06.01/0001 - R-10.06.01/0006 - RESTRICTED, 1990-1997 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Community Based Organizational Development and Empowerment: R-10.07.01/0001 - R-10.07.01/0017, 1996-2000 (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - CODE/ YES / LIST, Acham: reports, etc.: ®-10.07), 1997-2005 (Box 222, Folder 4-5)
    - Resources Interdependently Shared for Empowerment: R-10.08.01/0001 - R-10.08.01/0002, 1998-1999 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Dhading Resource Management Project: R-10.09.01/0001 - R-10.09.01/0011, 1998-1999 (Box 142B, Folder 3)
    - Dhading Resource Management Project - Reports: R-10.09.01/0003/001, R-10.09.01/0010, 1999 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Dhading Resource Management Project - Reports: R-10.09), 1998-2001 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Dhading Resource Management Project - Reports: R-10.09), 2002-2004 (Box 223, Folder 1-2)
    - Dhading Resource Management Project - Correspondence: R-10.09) - RESTRICTED, 2005 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Ramechhap Community Development Project: R-10.10.01/0001 - R-10.10.01/0014, 1998-1999 (Box 142B, Folder 4)
    - Ramechhap Community Development Project: General, reports, etc.: R-10.01), 1999-2001 (Box 223, Folder 4-6)
    - Ramechhap Community Development Project: General, reports, etc.: R-10.01), 2002-2004 (Box 224, Folder 1-4)
    - Morang: R-10.11.01/000- R-10.11.01/0005, 1998-2000 (Box 142B, Folder 4)
    - Morang: R-10.11), 2004-2005 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Nepali Organisations Unit. (NOU) / Resources Interdependently Shared for Empowerment (RISE): Reports, etc.: R-10.12), 1997-2000 (Box 224, Folder 6)
      For RISE see also R-10.08, O-02.03
    - Nepali Organisations Unit. (NOU) / Resources Interdependently Shared for Empowerment (RISE): Reports, etc.: R-10.12), 2001-2005 (Box 225, Folder 1-3)
    - NOU / NGO Support documents collected for evaluation 2001: R-10.12), 1996-2000 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - NOU Partner workshops: R-10.12), 2000-2002 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - NOU Partner workshops: R-10.12), 2003-2004 (Box 226, Folder 1-2)
    - NOU photo album: (R-10.12) (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Partnership Programme: reports, etc. R-10.13), 2002-2003 (Box 226, Folder 3-4)
      Continued after July 2003 as Partner Transition Team (T-11.05)
    - Partnership Programme: Nepal Bible Ashram: R-10.13), 2002-2006 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Promoting Sustainable Agriculture in Nepal (PSAN) / Nepal Permaculture Group: R-10.14), 1998-2003 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Rural Development Centre, Pokhara / Nucleus for Empowerment through Skill Transfer (NEST)
    - Reports, etc.: R-11.01.01/0001 - R-11.01.02/0030, 1979-1986 (Box 143, Folder 3-6)
    - Reports, etc.: R-11.01.02/0030 - R-11.01.03/0102, 1986-1992 (Box 144, Folder 1-6)
    - Reports, etc.: R-11.01.03/0034, R-11.01.03/0065 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc. - Workshop on Training: R-11.01.03/0046, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Reports,etc. - AHIP Evaluation: R-11.01.03/0077, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc.: R-11.01.04/0001 - R-11.01.05/0029, 1992-1999 (Box 145, Folder 1-4)
    - Reports,etc - "Social cost benefit analysis".: R-11.01.04/0014, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc. - "Training Needs Assessment Survey": R-11.01.04/0024, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc - "Impact evaluation of RDC": R-11.01.04/0038/001, 1996 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc. - "Training Village Animal Health workers..."" R-11.01.05/0004/001, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, etc.: R-11.02.01/0001 - R-11.02.01/0028 - RESTRICTED, 1980-1991 (Box 146, Folder 2-3)
    - Nepali NGO Program: R-11.03.01/0001 - R-11.03.01/0013, 1993-1998 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - 4th Year Evaluation: R-11.04.01/0001 - R-11.04.01/0005, 1995-1996 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Reports, etc.: R-11.05), 1994-2003 (Box 227, Folder 2-5)
    - Reports, etc., including NEST: R-11.05), 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 228, Folder 1-3)
    - Animal Health Training & Consultancy Centre: R-11.05), 2000-2002 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Training Management Team and Staff Management Committee meetings: R-11.06), 1993-1998 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Training Management Team and Staff Management Committee meetings: R-11.06), 1999-2001 (Box 229, Folder 1-3)
    - Quarterly Coordinating meetings: minutes: R-11.07), 2002-2004 (Box 229, Folder 4-5)
    - Leafltets, Training Course Information, 1999, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Rural Development: Income Generation
    - Income Generation General: R-12.01.01/0001 - R-12.01.01/0028 (location not listed in spreadsheet), 1981-1999
    - Food Drying and Processing: R-12.02.01/0005 (others from sequence R-12.02.01/0001 - R-12.02.01/0020 not listed in spreadsheet), 1984 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Grain Storage: R-12.03.01/0001 - R-12.03.01/0010, 1963-1984 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Oil Processing (other than Ginger): R-12.04.01/0001 - R-12.04.01/0010, 1984-1995 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Ginger: R-12.05.01/0001 - R-12.05.01/0020, 1977-1988 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Ginger: R-12.06.01/0010, 1980 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Crafts: R-12.06.01/0001 - R-12.06.01/0020, 1980-1989 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Crafts: Himalayan knitting: R-12.06.01/0010, 1980s (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - General Agriculture: R-12.07.01/0001 - R-12.07.01/0022, 1983-1991 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - General Agriculture: Basic vegetable gardening in Nepal: R-12.07.01/0022, 1991 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - General Agriculture: Ecologically orientated agriculture course: R-12.07.01/0021, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Animals: R-12.08.01/0001 - R-12.08.01/0022, 1980-1994 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Animals: Cattle and calving (in Nepali): R-12.08.01/0006 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Animals: Stall feeding in the hills of Nepal: R-12.08.01/0007, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Animals: How do you get healthy animals?: R-12.08.01/0015; JTA Handbook of animal health: R-12.08.01/0018, 1989-1990 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Animals: Animal Healthcare Training: R-12.08.01/0019, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Animals: Cattle health (in Nepali): R-12.08.01/0021 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Animals: Raising healthy pigs in the hills of Nepal: R-12.08.01/0023, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Animals: Handbooks on keeping goats and pigs (in Nepali): R-12.08.01/0024 - R-12.08.01/0027, 2000 (Box 165, Folder 4)
- S, Series XIX
  - Shanta Bhawan Project
    Including Cholera Hospital, District Clinics, Nursing School / Campus, New Hospital
    - Reports, etc.: S-01.01.01/0001 - S-01.01.01/0068, 1954-1971 (Box 147, Folder 2-4)
    - Reports, etc. S-01.01.02/0001- S-01.01.02/0048, 1971-1981 (Box 147, Folder 5-6)
    - Reports,etc. S-01.01.02/0025/001 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc.: S-01.01.02/0048 - S-01.01.02/0058, 1981-1982 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Reports,etc.: S-01.01.02/0057 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: S-01.02.01/0001 - S-01.02.01/0027 - RESTRICTED, 1961-1983 (Box 148, Folder 2-4)
    - Leases: S-01.03.01/0001-S-01.03.01/0015, 1956-1983 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Board Minutes: S-01.04.01, 1969-1982 (Box 148, Folder 5-6)
    - Constitution / By-Laws: S-01.05.01/0005 - S-01.05.01/0014, 1952-1977 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Statistics from Projects
    - Statistics for hospitals, clinics, community health, schools: S-02.00.01/0001 - S-02.00.01/0009, 1958-1976 (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
  - Surkhet Project
    - Reports, etc.: S-03.01.01/0001- S-03.01.01/0108, 1973-1988 (Box 149, Folder 4-6)
    - Reports, etc.: S-03.01.01/0079 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Reports, etc.: S-03.01.02/0001 - S-03.01.02/0062, 1989-1995 (Box 150, Folder 1-3)
    - Reports, etc. -"Voices in the Village...": S-03.01.02/0028, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc.: S-03.01.03/0001 - S-03.01.03/0034, 1996-1999 (Box 150, Folder 4-5)
    - Reports, etc.: S-03.01.03 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc. - Newspapers, Nepali: S-03.01.03/0005/001, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Reports, etc. - "Culture rather than organisation": S-03.01.03/0017, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc - Evaluation of project: S-03.01.03/0024, 1998 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Reports, etc.: (S-03.01), 1985-1997, 2000 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, etc.: S-03.02.01/0001 - S-03.02.01/0014 - RESTRICTED, 1974-1997 (Box 151, Folder 1-2)
    - Sahakarmi Samaj: General, reports, etc.: S-03.04, 1998-2005 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Other S
    - Swiss Friends for Mission in India and Nepal: S-04.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Swedish Free Mission: S-05.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Santal Mission: S-06.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Summer Institute of Linguistics: S-07.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Semri Dispensary: S-08-00-01 - (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Small Area Development Projects: S-09.00.01/0001 - S-09.00.01/0015, 1976-1979 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Southern Baptist Convention: S-10.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Syanga School Partnership Programme: reports, etc.: (S-11.00), 1999-2005 (Box 230, Folder 2-3)
    - Syanja: S-11.01.01/0001 - S-11.01.01/0012, 1996-1999 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Singapore Baptist Convention: S-12.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - SAAWE: S013.00.01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Security: Guidelines, plans, reports, briefings: (S-14.01), 1998-2005 (Box 230, Folder 4-5)
- T, Series XX
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Reports: T-01.01.01/0001 - T-01.01.01/0059, 1966-1985 (Box 151, Folder 5-6)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Reports: T-01.01.01/0060 - T-01.01.01/0091, 1985-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Reports: T-01.01.02/0001 - T-01.01.02/0073, 1990-1996 (Box 152, Folder 2-4)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Reports: T-01.01.03/0001 - T-01.01.03/0011, 1997-1998 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Correspondence: T-01.02.01 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Correspondence: (T-01.02) - RESTRICTED, 2003-2006 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Training and Scholarship Programme - "25 Years of Service" (1991); brochure re. Scholarship Programme (n.d.), 1991, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Training and Scholarship Program - Wilkins Memorial Trust: T-01.03.01 - NOT LISTED IN SPREADSHEET, 1994-1998
  - Theology of Development: T-02.00.01/0001 - T-02.00.01/0019, 1981-1999 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Theology of Development: T-02.00.01/0020 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - The Evangelical Alliance Mission: T-03.00.01 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - TEAR Fund, UK: T-04.00.01 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - TEAR Fund, UK: (T-04.00), 2003-2006 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - TEAR Fund, Holland, etc.: T-05.00.01 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Tibetan Work: T-06.00.01, 1963-1983 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Thankot: T-07.00.01 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Trekking and Travel in Nepal - Maps: T-08.01.01/0001 - T-08.01.01/0015 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Trekking and Travel in Nepal - J. Lindell trekking notes and booklets: T-08.02.01, 1957-1967 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Trekking and Travel in Nepal - Miscellaneous: T-08.03.01/0001 - T-08.03.01/0015, 1960-1992 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Training and Development: T-09.00.01/0001- T-09.00.01/0068, T-09.00.02, 1981-1999 (Box 154, Folder 2-4)
  - Training and Development: (T-09.00), 1998-2003 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - Tikapur: T-10.00.01/0001 - T-10.00.01/0013, 1972-1993 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Transition: Transition Team reports; (T-11.01), 2003-2008 (Box 231, Folder 1-2)
  - Transition: Transition Team meetings: minutes (T-11.02), 2003-2008 (Box 231, Folder 3-4)
  - Transition: Transition news updates, articles in Sahayatri, UMNews: (T-11.03), 2003-2006 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Transition: Institutions Transition Team: reports, etc.: (T-11.04), 2004-2005 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Transition: Partner Transition Team: reports, etc.: (T-11.05), 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    Continues former Partnership Programme C-10.13)
  - Transition: Partner Transition Team: Projects and Programmes Transitions Team: reports: (T-11.06), 2003-2005 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Transition: Partner Transition Team: Change Process: minutes, bulletins, progress reports: (T-11.07), 2001-2003 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - The UMN Strategic Change Process / B. Booth: (T-11), 2009 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    Includes CD of source documents
  - Contents of binder labeled "Change Process" (T-11), 2001-2005 (Box 252, Folder 1-3)
- U, Series XXI
  - United Mission to Nepal publications
    - UMNEWS (circular) renamed People Tree in 1991: U-01.00.01/0001- U-01.00.01/0002, 1977-1998 (Box 155, Folder 4-6)
      See UMNEWS (magazine) 1991-2006 below
    - UMN Circular: Sahayatri: U-01.00.02/0001, 1995-1998 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - UMN Circular: Sahayatri: Journeying Together (amalgam of People Tree and Sahayatri): U-01.00.02/0002, 1998-2006 (Box 155, Folder 2-3)
    - UMN Circular: Sahayatri: Journeying Together: various issues: (U-01) (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - UMNews (magazine): U-08.00.01 Numbers 1-15, 1991-2003 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - UMNews (magazine) Numbers 16-21, 23-27, 2004-2010 (Box 233, Folder 4)